Ian Yang

NO. 63, 10th Neighborhood, Zaoqiao Village, Zaoqiao Township, Miaoli County, Taiwan 36141 | ian.html@gmail.com

Summary -

Accomplished front-end web developer with 8 years of experience. Motivated web professional with extensive experience building static websites utilizing HTML, CSS and various web technologies. Able to complete projects efficiently and satisfy customers with quality codes.

Qualifications

- Semantic HTML markup
- Maintainable CSS code
- Website optimization

- Strong collaborative skills
- Excellent problem solving skills
- Industry knowledge

Technical Skills -

- HTML
- CSS
- SASS

- jQuery
- JavaScript
- Photoshop

Work Experience -

01/2011 - Current

Freelance Front-end Web Developer

Self-employed

- Leverage CSS media queries to implement mobile responsiveness.
- Develop HTML email templates and newsletters for email marketing campaigns.
- Maintain active conversation with clients to ensure products meet their needs.

05/2010 - 01/2011

Web Developer

XHTMLized - Melbourne, Australia

- Utilized advanced techniques to ensure pixel perfect and the quality of products.
- Worked closely with other developers and learned advanced version control skills.
- Maintained schedules and assured on-time delivery of code.

06/2008 - 05/2010

Freelance Front-end Web Developer

Self-employed

- Wrote W3C Valid HTML and CSS code to meet latest web standards.
- Created dynamic and interactive content through jQuery and JavaScript.
- Tested code in multiple browsers to ensure cross-browser compatability.

Education —

2009

Bachelor of Science: Entomology

National Chung Hsing University - Taichung, Taiwan